Finding Aid for William Sprague Studley Papers, 1846-1910
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
William Sprague Studley papers 1846-1910
Studley, William Sprague, 1823-1893.
0.6 linear ft. (in 2 boxes)
8692 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Harold S. Gray (donor no. 3393 ).
The collection is open to research.
Methodist Episcopal minister who ministered in Detroit and Ann Arbor, Michigan and Evanston, Illinois.
The collection is arranged into three small series: Correspondence, Studley Family, and Other Papers. Included in the collection is a scattering of correspondence, diaries, 1860 and 1873, of trip in Florida and Europe, a scrapbook, and newspaper clippings concerning the activities of the Studley family, 1855-1910.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Clergy--Michigan.; Detroit (Mich.); Europe--Description and travel.; Evanston (Ill.); Florida--Description and travel.; Illinois.; Methodist Episcopal Church--Illinois.; Methodist Episcopal Church--Michigan.; Southern states; Voyages and travels.
Contributors:
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909.; Willard, Frances Elizabeth, 1839-1898.
Genre Terms:
Diaries.; Scrapbooks.
- Correspondence
  - 1862-1873 (Box 1)
    (include letter from Edward Everett Hale, 1865)
  - 1874-1892 (Box 1)
    (include letters from James B. Angell, 1889 and Frances Wlllard, 1890-1891)
  - Letters of condolence, 1893 (Box 1)
    (include letter from Frances Willard, 1893)
- Studley Family
  - Papers, 1856-1907 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1855-1910, 4 folders (Box 1)
- Other papers
  - "Index Rerum" 1846 (Box 1)
  - Diary of trip to Florida and other Southern states, 1860 (Box 1)
  - Diary concerning trip to Europe, 1873 (Box 2)
  - Record of receipts and expenditures, 1868-1878 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1880-1881 (Box 2)